<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Kalcor</title>
    <link>http://kalcor.site/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Kalcor</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 19:14:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://kalcor.site/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Multi Theft Auto story</title>
      <link>http://kalcor.site/post/the-multi-theft-auto-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 19:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kalcor.site/post/the-multi-theft-auto-story/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The reason I&amp;rsquo;m writing this blog post is because I want to put this MTA shit to rest once and for all&amp;hellip;
I used to be a MTA developer, but I doubt you knew that. Probably because those MTA cretins did not credit me anywhere in their project, even though I worked with them for a year and came up with the main sync method (player context switching) which is used by both mods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I blocked Youtube from the SA-MP forums</title>
      <link>http://kalcor.site/post/why-i-blocked-youtube-from-the-samp-forums/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 13:54:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kalcor.site/post/why-i-blocked-youtube-from-the-samp-forums/</guid>
      <description>About a week ago I banned You(Them)tube from the SA-MP forums. This begs the question… “Why?”
On August 6th Infowars was banned from Youtube. Shortly after Apple, Spotify and Facebook (Being the ass sniffers they are) banned Infowars as well.
What happened to freedom of speech? Why are these brainwashed social justice warriors so butt hurt about the truth? If I want to get my news and information from a legitimate source instead of the CNN fake news corporation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My attempt at a versioning system</title>
      <link>http://kalcor.site/post/my-attempt-at-a-versioning-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 16:25:25 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kalcor.site/post/my-attempt-at-a-versioning-system/</guid>
      <description>Introduction If you have ever heard of SA-MP (San Andreas Mutliplayer), you might be familiar with the versioning system that I have created.
In my opinion, this versioning system is way better than Semver (Semantic Versioning) and any other versioning system out there.
So how does it work? Versioning starts at 0.0 and should be at 0.1 once it’s usable and ready for the public.
Major releases Every time you release a new major update, you increment the second number in the version by one.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>